After that day,
あの日を境にね、
After that day, Ming avoided me.
その日以来、明は私を避けるようになった。
That time, I thought Ming knew...
あの時、明は知っていると思った...。
that I was the same old Joe.
私はいつものジョーだった。
Joe, I'm sorry.
ジョー、すまない。
It's been you all along...
ずっとあなただった...。
Please come back to me, I'm begging you.
頼むから戻ってきてくれ。
But in the end,
しかし、結局は、
it's just about using my back and a replacement for someone.
自分の背中を使うことと、誰かの代わりをすることだ。
As always.
いつも通りだ。
Cut!
カット！
I think you could do better.
もっとうまくやれると思うよ。
Another take, Joe.
ジョー、また別のテイクだ。
When I realize, my life has repeated itself.
気がつけば、私の人生は繰り返されている。
I've become a place for emotional garbage dump of the two people,
私は2人の感情のゴミ捨て場になってしまった、
who made me die.
誰が私を死なせたのか。
Okay.
オーケー。
Oh, sorry, I've just finished packing.
ああ、ごめん、荷造りが終わったところなんだ。
Come with me. I'll give you a ride.
一緒に行こう。乗せてあげる。
It's alright.
大丈夫だよ。
I've told the crew that I'll go with the team's van.
クルーにはチームのバンで行くと伝えてある。
Your Mom's home, right?
ママは家にいるよね？
I just want to go say hello to her.
彼女に挨拶に行きたいんだ。
I'm back, Mom.
ただいま、ママ。
How was it, are you tired?
どうだった、疲れたか？
A little bit.
少しね。
Mom, this is Mr. Ming.
ママ、ミンさんだよ。
He's an investor of the movie that I'm playing.
彼は私が演じる映画の出資者なんだ。
Hello.
こんにちは。
I heard that you aren't doing very well.
あまり調子が良くないと聞いている。
So I wanted to visit.
だから行ってみたかったんだ。
Oh.
ああ。
This is good for your blood.
これは血液に良い。
Thank you.
ありがとう。
Excuse me, you look familiar.
失礼ですが、見覚えがあります。
Are you...
あなたは...
the presenter that I see often?
よく見る司会者は？
You have a great memory
あなたは素晴らしい記憶力を持っている
Joe, why didn't you tell me first, so I'd clean up the house?
ジョー、どうして最初に言ってくれなかったんだ？
It's alright, Ms.
大丈夫ですよ。
I won't be long.
長くはかからないよ。
Oh, yes.
ああ、そうだ。
Did you take this photo?
この写真はあなたが撮ったのですか？
Yes.
そうだ。
Joe must be about two or three years old.
ジョーは2、3歳だろう。
And how was he like back then?
その頃の彼はどうだった？
Oh, he's a very stubborn kid.
とても頑固な子なんだ。
He didn't listen to what I said.
彼は私の言うことを聞かなかった。
But luckily, he's not like that now.
でも幸いなことに、今はそんなことはない。
Why did he change?
なぜ彼は変わったのか？
I don't know that too.
それも分からない。
Because since he's waken up from coma,
昏睡状態から目覚めたからだ、
he becomes a very good kid. Like a different person.
彼はとてもいい子になる。まるで別人のようにね。
Er, Mom.
えー、ママ。
It's time for a dialysis.
透析の時間だ。
Darling, that's about in an hour.
ダーリン、あと1時間くらいだよ。
Well, the traffic is bad in the afternoon, Mom.
午後は交通の便が悪いのよ、ママ。
I think we should go now.
もう行った方がいいと思う。
Auntie Nual, auntie Nual.
ヌアルおばさん、ヌアルおばさん。
I think you should take Mom to the hospital now.
今すぐ母さんを病院に連れて行くべきだと思う。
Why are you in such a hurry?
なぜそんなに急ぐのですか？
Er...Mr...we'll talk again soon, alright?
ええと...ミスター...またすぐに話そう、いいね？
Right.
そうだね。
Ing, let's go to the hospital.
イング、病院に行こう。
Alright, take this too.
よし、これも持っていけ。
Thank you.
ありがとう。
See you again later.
また後で会おう。
Goodbye.
さようなら。
Take care of your friend.
友人をよろしく。
I will, Mom.
そうするよ、母さん。
Mr. Ming.
明さん。
You seem to be more interested in my story...
私の話に興味があるようだが...。
...than my Mom's well-being.
...母の幸福よりも。
But it seems like you don't want me to know.
でも、私に知られたくないようだね。
Well, I don't know what exactly you want from me.
君が僕に何を求めているのか、僕にはよくわからないよ。
How did you know
なぜそれを？
about how to act in the fencing scene in the first movie?
映画1作目のフェンシングのシーンでの演技の仕方について？
I just guessed.
私は推測しただけだ。
You do know, right?
知っているよね？
That Tong didn't play that scene himself.
トンはあのシーンを自分でプレーしていない。
Er...I...I don't know about that.
それはどうかな。
The person who knew about this had the same name as you.
このことを知っていた人物は、あなたと同じ名前だった。
He had the same figure.
体型も同じだった。
And he worked at the same place as you.
そして、彼はあなたと同じ職場で働いていた。
Most importantly, the day that he disappeared,
最も重要なのは、彼が姿を消した日だ、
was the day that you had an accident.
あなたが事故に遭った日です。
Do you think that this is all a coincidence?
これはすべて偶然だと思いますか？
Well, Mr. Ming...
さて、ミンさん...
I don't know what you're trying to say.
何を言いたいのか分からない。
Or are you saying...
それとも
are you thinking...
と思っているのか？
that he and I are the same person?
彼と私は同一人物だと？
I'm gonna get going now,
もう行くよ、
I have somewhere to go.
行くところがあるんだ。
Secretary Jim,
ジム長官
I'm not going to see the detective.
刑事には会わない。
There's someone I want to see more.
もっと見たい人がいる。
Mr. Ming had me collect all the images from the CCTVs....
明氏は私にCCTVからすべての画像を集めさせた......。
that were around Joe's place that night.
あの夜、ジョーの家の周りにいた人たちだ。
I believe that the thief must be close to Mr. Joe.
泥棒はジョーさんの近くにいるはずだ。
The two may know each other.
2人は知り合いかもしれない。
And isn't your boss here to see this too?
そして、あなたのボスはこれを見るためにここにいるのではないのですか？
Mr. Ming has just informed me that he has an urgent errand.
ミンさんから急用ができたと連絡があった。
So he told us to proceed.
だから、彼は私たちに進めと言った。
Sol.
ソル
You're the only one who saw the culprit.
犯人を見たのは君だけだ。
If you see someone suspicious, let us know right away.
不審な人物を見かけたら、すぐに知らせてください。
I will.
そうするよ。
Hey, he's not your friend. You can't just come here with a sudden appointment.
おい、彼は友達じゃないだろ。急に約束しても来れないよ。
And is he here?
彼はここにいるのか？
I don't know. His student is looking for him now.
私は知らない。教え子が今、彼を探している。
Hey, Ming.
やあ、ミン。
What's wrong with him?
彼はどうしたんだ？
I don't know.
分からないよ。
Since he's back from shooting a movie out of town,
郊外での映画撮影から戻ってきたからね、
he's changed.
彼は変わった。
I didn't go so I don't know what happened.
私は行かなかったので、何が起こったのかわからない。
I think this must involve that new stuntman.
あの新しいスタントマンが絡んでいるに違いない。
Sip some tea so you'll calm down.
お茶でも飲んで落ち着きなさい。
Do you know that I'd come here?
私がここに来ることを知っていますか？
Well, you're here
さて、あなたはここにいる
because you think I know the thing you're curious about, aren't you?
私がそのことを知っていると思っているから 気になるでしょ？
I met someone...
ある人に会ったんだ
He seems so much like Joe.
彼はジョーにとても似ている。
So much that I thought...
と思ったほどだ。
he might be the same person...
同一人物かもしれない...。
But how would that be possible?
しかし、そんなことが可能なのだろうか？
You were the one who told me that...
それを教えてくれたのは君だった...。
Joe is not dead nor alive.
ジョーは死んでいないし、生きているわけでもない。
Then please, Master, tell me where he is.
では、マスター、彼がどこにいるのか教えてください。
I really can't take this anymore.
もう本当に耐えられない。
Please.
頼むよ。
I will tell you...
教えてあげよう
only if you come meditate with me first.
まず私と一緒に瞑想してくれるならね」。
Please, Master, tell me.
マスター、教えてください。
I can only tell you about the direction.
私は方向性についてしか話せない。
But you must walk that path yourself.
しかし、その道は自分で歩まなければならない。
If you don't know, just say so.
知らないならそう言ってくれ。
It's alright
大丈夫だ
if you won't help me.
私を助けてくれないなら
I'll find the answer myself.
答えは自分で見つけるよ。
We've seen all of these...
我々はこれらすべてを見てきた...
and haven't found anyone yet.
まだ誰も見つけていない。
That night, Sol was confused about the time too.
その夜、ソルも時間を勘違いしていた。
So we had to rewatch everything again.
だから、もう一度すべてを見直さなければならなかった。
Starting from 11 p.m. till 5 a.m.
午後11時から午前5時まで。
I think this is the most suspicious one.
これが一番怪しいと思う。
Sol,
ソル
does he look like the one you saw that night?
あの夜見た人に似ている？
Who's that?
あれは誰だ？
How dare you break into this house?
よくもこの家に押し入ったものだ。
Do you know whose house this is?
誰の家かわかる？
So?
それで？
Is it him?
彼ですか？
Er...
えー...
No.
いや。
That day, he wasn't wearing this outfit.
その日、彼はこの服を着ていなかった。
Are you sure?
本当か？
Yes, let's continue.
そうだ、続けよう。
Please wait here.
ここでお待ちください。
I'll call you.
電話するよ。
Yes.
そうだ。
Thank you.
ありがとう。
Joe, this hospital looks so elegant.
ジョー、この病院はとてもエレガントに見えるよ。
Is it expensive?
高いですか？
It's alright, Mom. I can handle this for you.
大丈夫だよ、母さん。 私に任せてください
Hello, Auntie Ing.
こんにちは、イングおばさん。
Oh.
ああ。
Wut.
何だよ。
Hello. /  Hello.
こんにちは。/ こんにちは。
I heard from Joe that you're going to be here.
ジョーから君がここに来るって聞いたよ。
So I came to visit.
だから私は訪ねてきた。
Thank you so much.
本当にありがとう。
Wow, it's been a long time, you're doing good, Wut?
いやあ、久しぶりだね、 よくやってるよ。
Yes, I'm good.
はい、大丈夫です。
How about your Dad?
お父さんは？
My Dad is okay now too.
父ももう大丈夫だ。
Ma'am, this way, please.
こちらへどうぞ
Oh, right, right.
ああ、そうか、そうか。
Go, I'll follow you.
行ってくれ、私もついていく
Alright,
わかったよ、
see you later.
また後で
Yes, Mom.
そうだよ、ママ。
Goodbye, Mrs. Ing.
さようなら、イング夫人。
Have you eaten?
食事はした？
I'm thinking about going out to find something for my Mom to eat.
出かけることを考えている 母が食べるものを探すために。
Do you wanna tag along?
一緒に行く？
Mmm,
うーん、
I'm not hungry.
腹は減っていない。
You didn't come here because of my Mom, did you?
ママのためにここに来たんじゃないよね？
You know, there are so many rumors now.
今はいろいろな噂がある。
You and Ming are very close.
君とミンはとても仲がいい。
Is there anything I should know about?
何か知っておくべきことはありますか？
Well,
まあね、
Right now, I'm Mr. Ming's paramour.
今はミンさんの愛人なんだ。
You're a fool!
愚か者め！
Why would you do that?
なぜそんなことを？
Fame?
名声？
Money?
お金？
Huh?
え？
For money.
お金のためだ。
And for my Mom.
そして母に。
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
がっかりさせて申し訳ない。
And you'll regret this.
そして後悔することになる。
You came see me because of this, right?
そのために私に会いに来たんだろう？
I went to see images from CCTVs,
CCTVの映像を見に行った、
of Joe's house being intruded.
ジョーの家に侵入されたのだ。
And you know what,
それにね、
no one was suspicious.
誰も疑わなかった。
As if Ghost Joe came in and visited his own place.
まるでゴースト・ジョーがやってきたかのように そして自分の家を訪れた。
What?
え？
That's weird.
それは奇妙だ。
Yeah, and there are so many weird things.
ああ、それに変なことがたくさんある。
You know that Jojo's wife is a great cook.
ジョジョの妻が料理上手なのは知っているだろう。
And you told them that I told you about it.
そしてあなたは、私がそのことを話したと彼らに言った。
Hey, Joe,
やあ、ジョー、
I'd never said it.
言ったことはなかった。
Why did you lie?
なぜ嘘をついたのですか？
Huh?
え？
Sorry, I might have mistaken it for something else.
申し訳ありません。 他の何かのために。
Like when you remembered that I got twins?
あなたが思い出したときのように 双子を授かったと？
Joe, tell me the truth.
ジョー、本当のことを言ってくれ。
Talk to me, loud and clear. Now!
はっきり言ってくれ。今すぐに
Who the fuck are you?
お前は誰だ？
Why do you have so many things
なぜ、そんなに多くのものを持っているのか
in common with the person I used to know?
私が以前知っていた人物との共通点は？
Hey,
やあ、
tell me.
教えてくれ。
Er...I...
えー...私は...
Mr. Ming is calling for me now.
今、明さんが私を呼んでいる。
And Auntie Nual isn't home today, so I gotta bring my Mom home.
ヌアルおばさんも今日は家にいない、 だからママを家に連れて帰らなきゃいけないんだ。
Go wherever you need to go. I'm sorry.
どこへでも行ってくれ。ごめんなさい.
Shit, I don't know what the fuck is going on now.
くそっ、いったい何が起こっているんだ。
I'm so confused.
私はとても混乱している。
Go.
行くんだ。
It's alright.
大丈夫だよ。
Wait,
待ってくれ、
are you free the day after tomorrow?
明後日は空いてる？
There's an event coming.
イベントがあるんだ。
The money's good. Come with me.
金はいい。一緒に行こう
I'm busy on that day.
その日は忙しいんだ。
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい.
But thank you so much.
でも、本当にありがとう。
Alright, off you go. Talk to you later.
よし、行ってらっしゃい。また後で。
Goodbye
さようなら
Oh, Wut.
おお、すごい。
You're here to check on me?
私の様子を見に来たの？
Guys, leave us.
みんな、私たちから離れなさい。
I got something to talk to Sol.
ソルと話すことがあるんだ。
Tell me, you actually saw who the thief in the CCTV was, right?
実際に見たのか？ CCTVに映っていた泥棒は誰だったんだ？
Hey, I've already told you,
おい、もう言っただろう、
I don't see anyone.
誰もいないよ。
Sol.
ソル
How many years have I known you?
君を知って何年になる？
Do you think you can lie to me?
私に嘘がつけると思う？
And the guy that you saw...
君が見た男は...
was the new Joe, right?
が新しいジョーだったんだろ？
I'm sorry for being late.
遅くなって申し訳ない。
I had to drop my Mom off at the hospital.
母を病院に送り届けなければならなかった。
Have you eaten?
食事はした？
A bit.
少しね。
Cook for me.
僕のために料理してくれ。
I've prepared the stuff for you already.
もう用意してあるんだ。
Mr. Ming, if you're hungry,
ミンさん、もしお腹が空いているなら、
would you like me to order something for you to eat?
どうしましょうか？ 何かご注文は？
I want you to cook for me.
私のために料理を作ってほしい。
You haven't eaten anything, right?
何も食べていないんだろう？
Oh, wait, wait.
ああ、待って、待って。
Here...
ここで...
This is my recipe.
これが私のレシピだ。
Oh, wait.
ああ、待ってくれ。
How is it? Can you eat that?
どうですか？食べられる？
It's the same flavor I used to have.
以前食べていたのと同じ味だ。
I think anyone who makes instant noodles, gets the same flavor.
を作る人は誰でもそうだと思う。 インスタントラーメンも同じ味になる。
But there's something...
でも、何か...
that's unlike any noodles, definitely.
どの麺とも違う。
What is that?
それは何ですか？
I'll know when I finish this.
これを完成させたらわかるよ。
Mr. Ming.
明さん。
This is my restroom.
ここは私のトイレだ。
How could I not come in?
どうして入らなかったんだろう？
Mr. Ming.
明さん。
Mr. Ming!
明さん！
Joe,
ジョー
who exactly are you?
あなたはいったい何者なのですか？
I've already told you who I am.
私が誰であるかはすでに話した。
And why are you so much like him?
なぜ彼に似ているのですか？
Just tell me.
教えてくれ。
I can't take this anymore.
もう我慢できない。
Tell me the truth, please, I'm begging you.
お願いだから本当のことを言ってくれ。
Mr. Ming.
明さん。
If I were to tell you that I was him,
もし、私が彼だと言ったら...、
would you believe me, Mr. Ming?
信じてくれますか、ミンさん？
How would that kind of thing be possible?
そんなことが可能なのか？
Mr. Ming, accept it,
明さん、受け取ってください、
that Joe's dead.
ジョーは死んだ。
Joe is not dead!
ジョーは死んでいない！
He is!
彼はそうだ！
He is not!
彼は違う！
Get out!
出て行け！
Get out now!
今すぐ出て行け！
If I meditate,
瞑想すればね、
would you really tell me where Joe is?
本当にジョーの居場所を教えてくれるの？
Today, I brought you soup.
今日はスープを持ってきた。
You both can't remember me, right?
二人とも私のことは覚えていないんでしょう？
But this is Joe.
でも、これがジョーだ。
I'm so sorry
本当に申し訳ない
for not being able to take care of the body you created.
世話ができないからだ あなたが創った身体の。
Actually, I was supposed to be with you guys.
本当は、君たちと一緒にいるはずだったんだ。
But I don't know why I got into this Joe's body.
でも、なぜこのジョーの体に入ったのかはわからない。
But yeah, right now, I'm still alive.
でも、今はまだ生きている。
And there're people I need to take care.
それに、私が面倒を見なければならない人たちもいる。
So all I can do is...the best that I can do.
だから私にできることは...私にできるベストを尽くすことだけだ。
But don't you worry.
でも心配しないで。
Not long, one day, I'll be with you, Mom and Dad.
そう長くはない、 パパとママ、一緒にいるよ。
Joe.
ジョー
Is it really you?
本当にあなたなの？
Wut!
何だよ！
Wut, Wut, Wut, Wut, Wut!
ワット、ワット、ワット、ワット、ワット！
Wut! / Come here!
何だよ！/ こっちに来て
I told you not to go, didn't I?
行くなと言っただろう？
Why didn't you listen to me?
どうして私の言うことを聞かなかったの？
And why the fuck did you come back here?
なぜここに戻ってきたんだ？
I told you if you went, we weren't gonna be bros again.
行ったのなら言ったはずだ、 もう兄弟に戻るつもりはなかったんだ。
Wut, Wut, Wut, Wut, Wut!
ワット、ワット、ワット、ワット、ワット！
Wut! I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
うっ！ごめんなさい.本当にごめんなさい。
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
どうしてもっと早く言ってくれなかったの？
Do you know...
ご存知ですか？
how much everyone misses you?
みんな、どれだけ君に会いたがっている？
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい.
I'm so sorry.
本当に申し訳ない。
You're back!
戻ってきたね！
Right, Joe,
そうだね、ジョー、
you're back!
戻ってきた
I'm back.
戻ってきたよ。
I'm back here now.
今はここに戻ってきた。
I'm here.
私はここにいる。
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい.
It's alright.
大丈夫だよ。
How long do I have to sit here?
いつまでここに座っていればいいんだ？
Each person takes different durations to get to the top of the hill.
服用期間は人それぞれ 丘の頂上まで
Some get there slow, some fast.
そこに到達するのが遅い者もいれば、速い者もいる。
But they'll know they're at the top
しかし、彼らは自分たちがトップにいることを知るだろう
when they see the horizon.
水平線が見えたら
Good whiskey.
いいウイスキーだ。
Thanks.
ありがとう。
Joe, if it weren't for your parents,
ジョー、もし君の両親がいなかったらね、
I'd knock you out.
気絶させてやる
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい.
That's enough.
もう十分だ。
You've said sorry for hundreds of times already.
もう何百回も謝っただろう。
Why didn't you tell me when you were in the hospital?
なぜ言ってくれなかった 入院中は？
You wanted me to tell you?
私に言わせたかったの？
Let's give it a try...
試してみよう...。
Wut, hello.
こんにちは。
Wut, it's me, Joe.
僕だよ、ジョーだ。
Joe, your bro.
ジョー、兄弟だろ。
But now, I'm stuck in this body.
でも今は、この体から抜け出せない。
Please believe me, Wut.
信じてくれ、ウト。
Please.
頼むよ。
A fool would believe that.
馬鹿はそれを信じるだろう。
Right, if that really happened,
そうだね、もし本当にそうならね、
I would send you to the brain department to have your brain scanned.
私はあなたを脳部門に送りたい 脳をスキャンする
See? If I told you, you wouldn't believe me anyway.
ほらね。もし私がそう言ったら、 どうせ信じないだろうけど
But I wanted to tell you all everyday.
でも、毎日みんなに伝えたかったんだ。
I just didn't know how.
ただ、やり方がわからなかった。
But right now,
でも、今はね、
I'm so relieved.
安心したよ。
Who wrote the script of your life, man?
お前の人生の脚本は誰が書いたんだ？
We reunited.
私たちは再会した。
And it's all the same team.
しかも、すべて同じチームだ。
Tong...
トン...
Ming...
明...
What's this?
これは何だ？
I know.
分かっている。
I guess I haven't paid for the karma I did to them.
私が彼らにしたカルマの代償を払っていないようだ。
But it's alright.
でも大丈夫だ。
At least, this time...
少なくとも今回は...。
My goal tells me for whom I'm going to live.
目標は誰のために生きるかを教えてくれる。
You're so nice.
あなたはとても優しい。
You're doing this for her,
あなたは彼女のためにやっている、
and she's not even your real mother.
そして彼女はあなたの本当の母親ですらない。
Mrs. Ing is being so nice to me, and I'm not even her real son.
イングさんは私にとても親切にしてくれる、 僕は彼女の実の息子でもないしね。
This means a lot to an orphan like me, you know, Sol.
これは私のような孤児にとって大きな意味がある、 あのね、ソル。
Anyway...
とにかく...
Just you being alive, is good enough.
生きているだけで十分だ。
That was a nice thing to say.
いいことを言ったね。
Therefore, tonight,
だから、今夜は
cheers!
乾杯
And guys...
そしてみんな
If you're not drunk tonight, you can't go home!
今夜酔っ払っていなければね、 あなたは家に帰れない！
Cheers!
乾杯
And the food's already here, and you guys aren't eating it.
料理はもう来ているしね、 なのに、君たちは食べない。
Even I didn't have any evidence other than words.
私でさえ、言葉以外の証拠を持っていなかった。
But they believed me, wholeheartedly.
しかし、彼らは心から私を信じてくれた。
I guess this is what's called...
これがいわゆる...ということなのだろう。
a bond.
絆。
You might think I'm crazy.
私がおかしいと思うかもしれない。
But deep down, I still have hope...
でも、心の底ではまだ希望があるんだ...。
that my body is still out there somewhere.
私の体がまだどこかにあるということを。
Maybe that body is sleeping in a coma, somewhere.
その体は眠っているのかもしれない 昏睡状態のどこかで
And one day,
そしてある日、
I'm going to switch into that same old Joe's body.
に切り替えるつもりだ。 あの昔のジョーの体だ。
I think...
私は...
You've watched too many movies.
映画の見過ぎだ。
Nolan is really good, but it's an imaginary world.
ノーランは本当にいい、 しかし、それは想像上の世界だ。
Eat.
食べるんだ。
Whiskey! More whiskey!
ウイスキーもっとウイスキーを
Actually, you didn't have to give me a ride.
実は、乗せてくれなくてもよかったんだ。
I didn't wanna bother you.
迷惑をかけたくなかったんだ。
You being like this, it's just like the old Joe.
君はこんな感じだ、 昔のジョーみたいだ。
Well, I'm gonna get going now.
さて、そろそろ行くよ。
Hey, Joe.
やあ、ジョー。
Huh?
え？
Can I go in to visit your Mom?
ママに会いに行ってもいい？
Mom!
ママ
I'm back!
戻ってきたよ！
Hello.
こんにちは。
Let's see who gave me a ride home, Mom.
誰が家まで送ってくれたかな、ママ。
Hello. Hello.
こんにちはこんにちは。
Er...
えー...
Sol...the one...
ソル...あの...
that you were with in his music video, right?
彼のミュージック・ビデオに出演していましたよね？
Oh, you know me?
ああ、私を知っているのか？
Oh, of course, I know you. Please, welcome.
もちろん、私はあなたを知っている。 ようこそ。
Please, sit here.
ここに座ってください。
Hey, do you know that Nual and I are your fans.
ねえ、知ってる？ ヌアルと私はあなたのファンです。
Thank you.
ありがとう。
And your music videos,
ミュージックビデオも、
we've replayed them so many times, right?
何度も再生しているよね？
Really?
本当に？
Yes.
そうだ。
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございました。
Er...can I take a selfie with you?
あの...一緒に自撮りしてもいいですか？
I'll show it to the nurses.
看護師に見せるよ。
Of course.
もちろんだ。
I'll get you all some water.
水を持ってくるよ
Alright.
わかったよ。
May I?
よろしいですか？
Mom! Keep your cool.
ママ冷静に
Son, I'm this old. I don't need to be shy.
息子よ、私はこの年だ。恥ずかしがる必要はないよ。
Ah, let's do it. One. Two. Three.
ああ、やろう。ワンツースリー
Wow, you're so handsome.
うわぁ、ハンサムだね。
Right, my crew sent me the first draft of the music video...
クルーが送ってくれたんだ ミュージックビデオの第一稿...
Would you like to see it?
ご覧になりますか？
Yes!
そうだ！
Here. This is it.
ここだこれだ。
Let's see...
そうだな...
Wow,
ワオ、
Sol, you're so handsome.
ソル、君はとてもハンサムだ。
You shine so bright, like, wow.
あなたはとても輝いている。
Not that much...
それほどでも...。
For real.
本当だよ。
Mom, I'm in the video too.
母さん、僕もビデオに出てるよ。
Why aren't you talking about me at all?
なぜ私のことを一切話さないのですか？
Oh, there you are, Joe.
そこにいたのか、ジョー。
So?
それで？
You're handsome too.
君もハンサムだ。
But Sol...your smile...it's so sweet. Looking so good.
でも、ソル...君の笑顔は...とても優しいよ。 とてもいい感じだ。
Oh, no.
そんな。
Look at him, look at him!
彼を見ろ、彼を見ろ！
Joe, well, you're alright too.
ジョー、君も大丈夫だよ。
Can I beat Sol?
ソルに勝てるか？
Well...you're alright, you're alright.
まあ...大丈夫、大丈夫。
Sol, it's because of you, see?
ソル、それは君のせいなんだ。
My mom ignored me!
母は私を無視した！
But to me, you're always important.
でも、僕にとっては、君はいつも重要な存在なんだ。
I know that. I was just kidding.
それは分かっている。冗談だよ。
But I'm being serious.
でも、私は真剣なんだ。
Joe.
ジョー
Let me clear off your debts.
あなたの借金を清算させてください。
So you can be free from him.
だからあなたは彼から自由になれる。
Thanks, Sol.
ありがとう、ソル。
But I've chosen this path.
でも、私はこの道を選んだ。
And I gotta be responsible for it.
それに責任を持たなければならない。
Do you really think so
本当にそう思うか？
or do you still have feelings for him?
それとも、まだ彼に未練があるのですか？
Sol,
ソル
my feelings,
私の気持ち
they're dead with my old body.
彼らは私の老体とともに死んだ。
I have a chance to come back...
戻ってくるチャンスはあるんだが...。
I won't risk myself to get hurt like that again.
もうあんな怪我をするリスクは冒さない。
What's wrong with you?
どうしたんだ？
Is it really you?
本当にあなたなの？
I can't believe it.
信じられないよ。
I can't believe that I'd get to see you again.
また君に会えるなんて信じられないよ。
Thank you for not forgetting about me.
私のことを忘れないでいてくれてありがとう。
I'll never forget about you.
君のことは決して忘れないよ。
Joe is not dead...
ジョーは死んでいない
nor alive...
生きてもいない
Wait.
待ってくれ。
Have we met before?
以前にもお会いしましたか？
I think you've mistaken me for someone else.
私を誰かと勘違いしているようだ。
Wait.
待ってくれ。
What's your name?
お名前は？
My name is Joe.
僕はジョー。
Why did he change?
なぜ彼は変わったのか？
I don't know that too.
それも分からない。
Because since he's waken up from coma,
昏睡状態から目覚めたからだ、
he becomes a very good kid. Like a different person.
彼はとてもいい子になる。 まるで別人のように。
And
そして
action!
アクションだ！
It's not so different from the old guy.
年寄りとそんなに変わらないよ。
It's all the same.
全部同じだよ。
Who told you that?
誰がそんなことを言ったんだ？
From the back, he looks exactly like Tong.
後ろから 彼はトンにそっくりだ。
How is it? Can you eat?
どうですか？食べられますか？
It's the same flavor I used to have.
以前食べていたのと同じ味だ。
The person who knew about this had the same name as you.
について知っていた。 これはあなたと同じ名前だった。
He had the same figure.
体型も同じだった。
And he worked at the same place as you.
そして、彼はあなたと同じ職場で働いていた。
Most importantly,
最も重要なことだ、
the day that he disappeared,
あの日、彼は姿を消した、
was the day that you had an accident.
あなたが事故に遭った日です。
Do you think it's all a coincidence?
すべて偶然だと思いますか？
Joe, I'm sorry.
ジョー、すまない。
It's always been you, all along.
ずっと、ずっとあなただった。
Please come back to me,
私のところに戻ってきてください、
I'm begging you.
お願いだ。
If I told you that I was him,
もし私が彼だと言ったら
would you believe me, Mr. Ming?
信じてくれますか、ミンさん？
Have you got the answer?
答えは出たのか？
It's the opposite.
その逆だ。
I've got so many questions.
質問がたくさんあるんだ。
Impossible questions.
不可能な質問だ。
Or the answer is very clear itself?
それとも、答えははっきりしているのか？
And you just can't accept it?
それを受け入れられないのか？
But those answers...
しかし、その答えは...
are hard to believe too.
も信じがたい。
The truth...
真実は...
sometimes, you cannot see it with your eyes.
目では見えないこともある。
And what should I do?
どうすればいいんだ？
Ask yourself.
自分自身に問いかけてみてほしい。
If there's something wrong, please call us right away.
何か問題があれば すぐにお電話ください。
I will, thank you.
そうするよ。
Thank you.
ありがとう。
Are you cold, Mom? I'll cover you with the blanket.
ママ、寒くない？ 毛布をかけてあげる。
Thank you, darling.
ありがとう、ダーリン。
Eh...You seem happy these days.
最近は幸せそうだね。
Is there anything?
何かありますか？
Nothing.
何もない。
I'm happy because I see you get better each day.
私が幸せなのは 日に日に良くなっているようだね。
Not because that singer gave you a ride home?
あの歌手が家まで送ってくれたからじゃないの？
You mean, Sol?
ソルのことか？
Yeah.
そうだね。
C'mon, I'm an old lady.
おいおい、私はおばさんだよ。
I can tell that he likes my son.
彼が私の息子を好きなのはわかる。
But...do you like him?
でも...彼のことは好き？
Mom, I got so much work. I don't have time to take care of anyone else.
母さん、仕事がたくさんあるんだ。 他の人の面倒を見ている時間はないんだ。
Joe. I'm old.
ジョーもう年だ。
I...would like someone to take care of you
私は...誰かにあなたの面倒を見てもらいたい
when I'm not around anymore.
私がいなくなったらね
Mom, why did you say that?
ママ、どうしてそんなことを言ったの？
You're still healthy.
あなたはまだ健康だ。
You gotta be with me for a long long time, alright?
私と一緒にいて 長い長い間だ、いいか？
I just wanna get to see who's going to take care of you instead of me.
私はただ、誰が行くのか見たいだけなんだ 私の代わりにあなたの面倒を見る。
Just you being happy, I'm okay with anyone.
ただ、あなたが幸せでいること、 僕は誰でもいいんだ。
Thank you, Mom.
ありがとう、母さん。
Right, Mom...
そう、ママ...
you used to tell me that...
よくそう言っていたね...
my Dad died when I was little, right?
僕の父は僕が小さい頃に死んだんだよね？
Yeah, I think you were...
ああ、君は...
about seven years old.
約7歳。
Seven years old.
7歳だ。
Then, you only had a few years with him.
それなら、彼と一緒にいられたのはほんの数年しかない。
If you could turn back time,
もし時間を戻せるとしたら、
would you change your mind and choose someone else?
気が変わったか そして他の誰かを選ぶのか？
If it were your Dad, Joe,
もし君のお父さんだったら、ジョー、
no matter how many times I had to turn back time,
何度 私は時間を戻さなければならなかった、
I would still choose your Dad.
私なら、やっぱりお父さんを選ぶね。
Yes, Mom.
そうだよ、ママ。
You're the sweetest.
あなたは最高に優しい。
Speaking of him makes me miss him.
彼のことを話すと懐かしくなる。
Just a sec.
ちょっと待ってくれ。
Come see me ASAP.
大至急、私に会いに来てください。
Please.
頼むよ。
I was the one who called you.
君を呼んだのは僕だ。
I'm Mike, Ming's brother.
僕はマイク、ミンの弟だ。
Yes.
そうだ。
And is there anything you want to talk to me?
私に話したいことはある？
I just want to see with my own eyes...
この目で確かめたいんだ...。
the person who...
は
made my brother go meditate.
弟を瞑想に行かせた。
What do you mean?
どういう意味ですか？
What's your name?
お名前は？
My name is Joe.
僕はジョー。
Oh, that's why he's into you.
だから彼は君に夢中なんだ。
I'm just a toy for you brother to play with when he's lonely.
私はあなたのおもちゃよ 寂しいときに一緒に遊ぶためにね
A toy that's worth five million Baht and a house?
価値あるおもちゃ 500万バーツと家？
Isn't that too expensive?
それは高すぎないか？
It's just a piece of money to you all.
君たちにとってはただのカネだ。
But for me,
でも私にとっては、
it changes my life and my Mom's too.
それは私の人生を変え、私の母も変える。
But don't you worry...
でも、心配しないで...。
because one year after this...
この1年後に...
I won't come see your brother anymore.
もうお兄さんには会いに行かない。
How can I believe that you're gonna keep your promise?
どうしたら信じられるだろうか。 約束は守るのか？
Well, your kind of people...
まあ、君たちのような人たちは...。
Making one stuntman disappear...
一人のスタントマンを消す...
isn't so difficult, right?
そんなに難しくないだろう？
You should worry about your brother.
弟のことを心配するべきだ。
Is he going to let me go or not?
彼は私を解放するつもりなのか、しないつもりなのか？
Well.
まあね。
You don't seem like you're a golddigger I used to meet.
あなたはそんな風には見えない。 君は昔会った金食い虫だ。
What are you doing here?
ここで何をしているんだ？
You let him in?
中に入れたのか？
I'm sorry, Mr. Ming.
申し訳ありません、ミンさん。
I had Secretary Jim call him in.
ジム長官に彼を呼ばせた。
Who told you to mess with my life?
誰が私の人生に干渉しろと言った？
Then, I guess...excuse me.
では、失礼します。
Wait.
待ってくれ。
You must come with me.
私と一緒に来るんだ。
Do not follow us.
私たちについて来るな。
We're going alone.
僕たちだけで行くんだ。
Whose car is this?
これは誰の車ですか？
Get in.
乗れ。
And where would you like me to go?
どこに行けばいい？
Just take me anywhere.
どこへでも連れて行ってくれ。
Mr. Ming.
明さん。
I don't know where to take you.
どこに連れて行けばいいのか分からない。
If you don't know where to take me,
私をどこに連れて行けばいいかわからないなら、
there's one place I want to go.
行きたいところがあるんだ。
I wanna get up there.
あそこに行きたいんだ。
Are you sure, Mr. Ming?
本当ですか、ミンさん？
Why, don't you want to?
どうして、そうしたくないの？
Mr. Ming, I think it looks dangerous.
明さん、危なっかしいと思いますよ。
We...we should go back, Mr. Ming.
我々は...戻るべきだよ、ミンさん。
Walk carefully. My place is a little dark.
気をつけて歩いてください。私の家は少し暗い。
This time,
今回はそうだ、
I can't tell if the feelings that I have...
私が抱いている感情は...。
belongs to this body...
この体に属している...
or the old body...
あるいは古い体...。
But no matter what,
しかし、何があってもだ、
I guess it doesn't matter anymore.
もうどうでもいいことだと思う。
Has Wut ever told you...
ウトから聞いたことがあるか？
that the old Joe's house was intruded?
オールド・ジョーの家に侵入されたのですか？
Yeah.
そうだね。
The detective said that there's no trace of damage on the door.
刑事はこう言った。 ドアに損傷の痕跡はない。
That means the thief used the spare key to get in.
つまり、泥棒は スペアキーで中に入った。
And in this world...
そしてこの世界では...
the people who know where the spare key is are...
知る人ぞ知る スペアキーはどこにある？
me,
私だ、
Sol...
ソル...
and you.
そして君だ。
Right, Joe?
そうだろ、ジョー？
Mr. Ming!
明さん！
Could you stop joking?
冗談はやめてくれないか？
I've already told you Mr. Ming is d...
ミン氏は...
Not dead!
死んでいない！
Nor alive!
生きているわけでもない！
Because he's back in the new body.
新しい体に戻ったからだ。
Mr. Ming, what are you talking about?
ミンさん、何を言っているんですか？
You could lie to me
あなたは私に嘘をつくことができる
but your body told me all the answers.
でも、あなたの体がすべての答えを教えてくれた。
There's only one person....
たった一人しかいない......。
who sneezes when reaching orgasms.
オーガズムに達するときにくしゃみをする人。
Ming, do you like doing it from the back?
ミン、後ろからやるのは好き？
And you don't like it?
それが気に入らないのか？
What?
え？
We've found Joe.
ジョーを見つけたよ。
Are you sure?
本当か？
Yes, Mr. Ming.
はい、ミンさん。
They've found Joe.
ジョーが見つかった。